

Natalya Sentemova

Frontend developer

Address: Armenia, Gyumri

Phone: +3043068596

Email: ns.sent@yandex.ru

Website: resume

https://t.me/TaliSent

LinkedIn /natalya

Telegram:

Web-dev Skills

Figma

React

Vanilla Js

Typescript

HTML

CSS

Frontend developer with about 3 years of experience. Skilled at React.js, Typescript, HTML & CSS, Figma. Worked in a team of specialists and as a sole developer on 6 very different projects in total. Quickly learn all the required technologies. Interested in relocation. Most often described by collegues as "nice to communicate with":)

Resume

Education

2012 – 2018 — Moscow State University

Moscow

Bachelor of Physics

Predicted electron fluxes with neural networks, data proccesing with Python and Numpy

2021 - Codeacademy

Online

Learn React Course

2021 - CodeacademyLearn React Part II Course

Online

2021 — Zar Zakcharov

Online

React Maraphon

A month of intense work on a small card game

Employment

Aug 2018 — May 2019 - AT Consulting

Moscow

QA Engineer

- tested widgets, written in Java + SQL
- worked with databases and creating test data (MySQL)
- provided automation testing support

Aug 2018 — May 2019 - AT Consulting

Moscow

Junior web-developer

• writed SQL queries for widgets and printed forms

Oct 2019 - Present - Cinimex

Moscow

Frontend developer

- developed web applications with React.js, Redux, TypeScript, Node.js, Jest, Thrifts, Sass, BEM, Styled Components, material-ui, etc.
- Jira & Git, Kibana, Maraphon
- Figma